
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is the sum of angle at a point?",
    answer: "360",
    options: [
      "120",
     " 270",
      "360",
     " 180"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following are pythagoras Triple",
    answer: "3,4,5",
    options: [
      "3,2,1",
      "5,3,1",
      "1,2,3",
      "3,4,5"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is a decagon?",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "10",
      "20",
      " Both a and d",
      "5"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Simplify 2*6(25/5)-3",
    answer: "57",
    options: [
      "23",
      "116",
      "60",
      "57"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " which of the following angle is the sum of interior angle of a regular polygon",
    answer: "90",
    options: [
      "180",
      "270",
      "45",
      "90"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "All are quadrilateral triangle except",
    answer: "circle",
    options: [
      "kite",
      "parallelogram",
      "circle",
      "square"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the square-root of 256",
    answer: "16",
    options: [
      "16",
      "12",
      "18",
      "14"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Factorize (6x-2x)(3x-x)",
    answer: "3x+1",
    options: [
      "2x+1",
      "3x-2",
      "2x+2",
      "3x+1"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the sum of angle on a straight line",
    answer: "180",
    options: [
      "90",
      "360",
      "180",
      "45"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Expand (6x-3x)(6x+3x)",
    answer: "12x+3x+9",
    options: [
      "6x+3x-1",
      "24x+12x+3",
      "12x+3x+9",
      "9x+2x-6"
    ]
  },
];